{
    "id": "addaf00fe91a445e8dd60d0a08cd1637",
    "title": "Present Perfect Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Jane ............................... from office.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "returns",
                "returned",
                "has returned"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She ................................... a novel.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wrote",
                "has written",
                "have written"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ...................................... in ten films.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "acted",
                "has acted",
                "have acted"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ................................. not received your letter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "has",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have never ................................ of that place.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hearing",
                "heard",
                "hearded"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ................................... lost her money.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Look, what John ................................... me!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gave",
                "has given",
                "had given"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Police .................................... 80 suspected drug traffickers in raids.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has arrested",
                "have arrested",
                "had arrested"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A 24-year old woman ....................................... killed in an accident.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "has",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Honey, I ..................................... my keys.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have lossed",
                "have lost",
                "have losed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................. six phone calls since lunchtime.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have answered",
                "had answered",
                "has answered"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}